(Dr Hofstadter:)Logging off.
(Amy:)Ninety-nine...
...100.
(Amy:)It's like a waterfall of liquid gold.
(Amy:)My turn.
Don't know what the point of staying
in L.A. is.
(Penny:)I haven't gotten a single acting job
since I moved out here.
The closest I came was Iast month. I got
a callback for a hemorrhoid commercial.
(Amy:)Oh, I could so see you
being the face of hemorrhoids.
(Penny:)I know, right?
Ugh, maybe I should just move back
to Nebraska.
- No, I can't let you do that.
- Why not?
(Amy:)For the first time ever,
I have a thriving social life.
(Amy:)And no pressure,
but it kind of lives and dies with you.
(Raj:)Hi, Amy, can I talk to Penny?
(Amy:)A guest in my trundle bed
and a boy at my door?